Coming to a screen bigger than your TV.
Beavis and Butt-Head Do America is a animation, comedy,
adventure film directed by Mike Judge.
Slacker duo Beavis and Butt-Head wake to discover their TV has been stolen.
Their search for a new one takes them on a clueless adventure across America,
during which they manage to accidentally become America's most wanted.
Beavis / Butt-Head / Tom Anderson (Old Guy With Camper) / Van Driessen (Hippie
Teacher) / Principal McVicker (voice), played by Mike Judge.
Muddy (voice), played by Bruce Willis.
Dallas (voice), played by Demi Moore.
Old Woman On Plane and Bus (voice), played by Cloris Leachman.
Agent Flemming (voice), played by Robert Stack.
Agent Hurly (voice), played by Jacqueline Barba.
Beavis and Butt-Head Do America is a 1996 American adult animated comedy road film
based on the MTV animated television series Beavis and Butt-Head.
The film was co-written and directed by series creator Mike Judge, who also reprises his roles from the
series; Demi Moore, Bruce Willis, Robert Stack and Cloris Leachman star in supporting roles.
The film follows Beavis and Butt-Head, two teen slackers who travel the US in
search of their stolen television and unknowingly become fugitives.
Previous offers by MTV to adapt Beavis and Butt-Head to film were rejected
by Judge, before he eventually agreed to the film in 1994.
As production began, the series' staff halted production while
Judge wrote the screenplay with Joe Stillman.
John Frizzell composed the film's score.
Beavis and Butt-Head Do America premiered at Mann's Chinese Theater on December 15, 1996, and
was released in the United States on December 20, 1996, by Paramount Pictures.
The film later aired on MTV in 1999.
The film was a critical and commercial success, with critics praising the story and humor, and grossing $63.1 million in the United States and becoming the largest December box office opening of all time
until it was surpassed the following year by Scream 2, and was the second highest-grossing animated film of 1996, behind Disney's The Hunchback of Notre Dame (which also starred Moore).
A sequel, Beavis and Butt-Head Do the Universe, was released in 2022.
The film explores themes of hotel, sperm, washington dc, usa, casino, fbi.
The tone is lighthearted.